<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JoeyChor&#39;s Website</title>
    <description>Random articles about random topics</description>
    <link>http://joeychor.me</link>
    <atom:link href="http://joeychor.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Triple A Games&amp;#58; Why it&#39;s bad</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you ever played “Triple A” or AAA games, you find that it’s usually better quality than games that aren’t.
However, really any game can be labeled as “Triple A.”
This lack of regulation of what a “Triple A” game is bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first reason that this is bad is because there is simply no regulation. Consider an SSL certificate (if you do not know what an SSL
certificate is, it is used to encrypt your content from hackers over the Internet). On your system, there is a list of certificates to
trust. If you connect to, let us say a bank, and the bank’s certificate is a trusted one, everything goes on normally. If it is not, the
Internet browser would normally terminate the session because it is not trusted. A limited number of people can give out certificates.
If everyone could have their own certificates, then any malicious user can say that their to be trusted. This tricks you into trusting
security with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second reason why it is bad is because it is defined by a community rather than an organization. Large gaming communities like IGN and GameSpot,
control what is a “Triple A” game. A part of these communities genuinely believe that a game really deserves a “Triple A” title.
There have been multiple reports on IGN(&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.zeldainformer.com/news/former-ign-employee-admits-review-scores-are-skewed-due-to-public-relations&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;,
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.p4rgaming.com/ex-ign-employee-leaks-list-of-review-scores-for-games-that-arent-even-close-to-release-like-gta-v/&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.screwattack.com/news/ex-ign-employee-admits-reviews-were-swayed-money&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;) and GameSpot (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tomshardware.com/forum/34016-13-gamespot-biased&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;, 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamespot.com/articles/what-games-console-should-i-buy/1100-6423839/&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.psu.com/forums/showthread.php/101455-A-Hard-Look-At-Gamespot-(Bias-in-Review-Scores-Comparison)&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;) where they either are payed to vote
positively or just side on one console and switch to another. Even then, they think that the “Triple A” games are now useless (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ign.com/articles/2012/07/30/are-aaa-hardcore-games-doomed&quot;&gt;IGN&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamespot.com/videos/the-point-how-content-is-killing-aaa-games/2300-6423625/&quot;&gt;GameSpot&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last reason why it is bad is because of simple psychology. If someone has an original game with different game mechanics, you might get that.
However, if someone else has a same game with same game mechanics, but labeled as “Triple A,” you will get that because of two reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is a game with same mechanics as the predecessors. You already know how to play the game, and jump right into it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Does not “Triple A” sound good? It is because of the school system almost everywhere—an “A” score is very good, so imagine it being three
times as good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While now you may think that is silly, it sneaks up behind you when you don’t have this article in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude, a “Triple A” game is bad because there is no regulation, defined by a community, and is controlled by psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://joeychor.me/Triple-A-Games/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joeychor.me/Triple-A-Games/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sticking with the existing projects!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided that instead of making a whole new website, I stick with something that many people have access to—a program called Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really useful for starting up a blog quickly. Luckily, Jekyll doesn’t use any dynamic webpages, so it can be hosted anywhere that accepts HTML pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I also want to make money, and a way that I had planned was to use a URL shortener to their webservers, much like adf.ly. But until I get used to this Jekyll, all links linked are going to be direct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to donate &lt;a href=&quot;http://joeychor.me/donate.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://joeychor.me/Stick-To-Existing-Projects/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joeychor.me/Stick-To-Existing-Projects/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Donations</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you want to donate, I have 6 cryptocurrency addresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin: 1BURX86JJrzGm9irf5e3bpabxTaMxbS1pZ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Litecoin: LKcNFAys2CSidSzMytpbgAePyvuyq6iQmJ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dogecoin: DR4bebgD9EdAnJ3iPSAACZkUaRA61Acwgg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clam: xL2LvuTzD5fpdDRnpQ6s5xewYL9awPy71R&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dash: XiLWDVUBEtxxDQ1e4XSshwhUmt9e4byvxM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vericoin: VAje8dPrXDZKgw23dJpX86KPDHVJmNgMMU&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any donation is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://joeychor.me/donate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://joeychor.me/donate.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>